

Details

Dublin Ireland 0830233442 albxdbert@gmail.com

Links

My GitHub

Linkedin

Skills

Ability to Work in a Team

Communication Skills

Customer Service

Computer Skills

Java

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript

Nodejs

SQL

MongoDB

Python

Microsoft Excel

React

Git

Languages

Russian

English

Profile

I am a third-year student from Griffith College Dublin studying Computing Science Honors degree. As a part of the course, I am required to do work placement. I am experienced with:

- Java
- JUnit
- Web development (HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, React, Nodejs)
- Databases (SQL, MongoDB)
- Data Analytics (Python, Excel)
- Selenium

I can be flexible and I would be glad to get a job in the area of Computing Science.

Education

Computing Science, Griffith College Dublin, Dublin

SEPTEMBER 2020 - MAY 2024

Gained self learning skills, the skills of working in a team, and computer skills.

By the time I graduate, I will get the Computing Science Honors degree that says that I completed the course.

Employment History

Bar Back, HYATT, Dublin

SEPTEMBER 2021 - JANUARY 2022

- Monitored bar inventory and made notes for needed supplies when necessary.
- Worked well with other bar and restaurant staff.
- Maintained a clean and orderly bar.
- Acted as a support to other bartenders by creating drinks, and helping to maintain and stock the bar when necessary.

Customer Service Representative, Domino's Pizza, Dublin

FEBRUARY 2022 - JULY 2022

- Provided customers with quality assistance through phone calls, emails, and internet chats.
- Built a strong working knowledge of the company procedures and protocols.
- Answered phone calls and provided callers with pertinent information and assistance.
- Developed a strong working knowledge of products and offerings.